question_data = {"results": [{"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                              "question": "Leonardo da Vinci&#039;s Mona Lisa does not have "
                                          "eyebrows.", "correct_answer": "True",
                              "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                             {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                              "question": "There was a satirical candidate named &quot;Deez "
                                          "Nuts&quot; running in the 2016 US presidential "
                                          "elections.", "correct_answer": "True",
                              "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                             {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean",
                              "difficulty": "easy",
                              "question": "A universal set, or a set that contains all sets, "
                                          "exists.", "correct_answer": "False",
                              "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                             {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean",
                              "difficulty": "easy",
                              "question": "The word &quot;Inception&quot; "
                                          "came from the 2010 blockbuster hit &quot;Inception&quot;.",
                              "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                             {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                              "question": "Peyton Manning retired after winning Super Bowl XLIX.",
                              "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                             {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean",
                              "difficulty": "easy",
                              "question": "The game &quot;Battlefield 1&quot; takes place during World War I.",
                              "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                             {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                              "question": "There are no deserts in Europe.",
                              "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                             {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                              "question": "Rabbits are rodents.", "correct_answer": "False",
                              "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                             {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                              "question": "In World War ll, Great Britian "
                                          "used inflatable tanks on the ports of Great Britain to divert "
                                          "Hitler away from Normandy \/ D-day "
                                          "landing.",
                              "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                             {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean",
                              "difficulty": "easy",
                              "question": "John Williams composed the music for &quot;Star Wars&quot;.",
                              "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]}
